

MEET GADA

ABOUT ME

Currently studying as under graduate student in the Department of Electronics and Telecommunications Engineering, I love to create digital designs and artwork and have been working in the field of Graphic Designing and Video Editing for more than 3 years. I am a passionate person and love to explore new things in various array of skills and hobbies.



PROFILE

132, Bora Bazar, 4th Floor, Room no. 6A Fort. Mumbai-01

meetgada2307@gmail.com +91 8169388385

CHARACTERISTICS

- Friendly
- Fast learner
- · Always want to improve
- Creative
- Unflappable

SOFTWARES KNOWN

Photoshop
illustrator
CorelDraw
Premiere Pro
After Effects
Blender

EDUCATION

B. Tech

KJ Somaiya College of Engineering, Vidyavihar 2019 - 2023

Junior College Jai Hind College, Mumbai 2017 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

Creative Head

KJSCE Students' Council 2021-2022

Asst. Art Director

Team Kshitij 2021

Jt. Creative Head

KJSCE Students' Council 2020-2021

Editorial Board - Creative Team

Team Kshitij 2020



